Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Got to get up.
I'm working on it.
Seriously. Jeb. it's time to go.
You found one for us?
What the hell?
Storm's here. guys! Let's go!
Nah. Nah. it can't be.
God. I went way too
hard last night.
Javi. get up. Come on.
Oh! Come on!
Where are the trash bags?
Oh. Found 'em.
Jeb. are you sure
you're recording?
- I don't see a red light.
- Oh.
- Yeah. Recording.
- Okay.
Blah.
Don't make me laugh. Stop it.
Okay.
Today. our science team
from the Tornado Tamer
project is out in the field.
about to chase a
storm southwest of us.
Our experiment is designed
to decrease the moisture
inside of a tornado to see
if we can make it collapse.
Tell the folks how
you do that. Kate.
Well. first. we got
to find a tornado
to suck up our superabsorbent
polymers in these barrels...
Diapers.
Tell them it's the same stuff
they use in diapers. Hmm.
Oh. yeah. It's nontoxic.
Uh. the Doppler doesn't show
a storm until the afternoon.
The data doesn't see
what Kate sees. remember?
How about Kate sees a
few more hours of sleep?
That might work.
Praveen. what are you doing?
Dorothy's not a desk.
Come on. Get in.
get in. get in!
Ready? You know what today is?
The day we tame a tornado!
- Yeah!
- All right.
I'm gonna yak first.
Ow.
- Yeah!
♪ Whine it. whine it ♪
♪ Pon di bank ♪
- ♪ Whine it. whine it ♪
- ♪ Pon di bank ♪
- ♪ Salio el sol ♪
♪ Pon di river ♪
- ♪ Pon di river ♪
- ♪ Salio el sol ♪
♪ Pon di bank... ♪
Kate was right. Southeast
winds are picking up.
Here they are.
It's really building up.
♪ Salio el sol... ♪
One Mississippi.
two Mississippi...
That's not a thing. by the way.
Hey. Mom. What's
up? Yes. it is.
Yeah. yeah. just
chasing weather around.
It's a thing. Mm-mm.
Yes. we'll be
careful. I promise.
Hey. Mrs. Carter.
- Hey!
- Hey. Mrs. Carter!
- We miss you.
Hello.
Okay. I'll tell 'em. Got to go.
Uh. she says there's barbecue
at the house when we're done.
- Oh. yes. Thank you.
- Yes. Cathy. Yes.
Man. I love Oklahoma.
All right. how are we
getting to this thing?
I'll need a southwest position
to read my sensors.
Yeah. coming right up.
One Mississi...
Oh.
Oh. and the wind
shear is strong.
Got some serious energy
building in there.
Oh. hey. Hey. buckle up.
Don't... Don't lean
out the window.
Come on. Come back in.
Addy. that's... Please?
Ever since you got struck
by lightning. you're no fun.
Yeah. well. that's what happens.
Mm.
Okay. we should get
the mixture ready.
Uh. don't you want to wait
for the rain to hit first?
Okay. we should. um...
We should get the mixture ready.
Yes. we should.
Jeb! Yep.
Come on! Okay.
I'm mixing.
You have to mix it.
- I got it. I got it.
Here she is! That
should be enough.
All right.
- Okay.
Okay. we're good.
Hey. hey. look.
Hey. gentle. gentle.
Like... Right? Come on.
Now try.
Usually it works. but...
This thing is so old.
Like. I mean. it's old. but
it's field-tested. you know?
Unlike Kate's science
project over here.
It's our science project.
No time. Javi.
If Dorothy's not working.
then forget the data. okay?
- We'll worry about it later.
- "Forget the data"? What is...
The tornado's not gonna
wait for us. Javi.
There's a death
ridge setting in.
Probably our last
chase of the season.
No matter what. we got to
get these barrels in the air
and see if they can make
a tornado vanish. okay?
It's more important.
No. how about it's equally as
important we do both. right?
Look. look. if you make a
tornado vanish with this.
but you don't get
the data with this.
who's gonna believe it?
Oh. Got it.
Fine. Get us the numbers.
Whatever we need to
win a big fat grant.
Well. I'm all about
my cash money. right?
Yeah.
You ready? Let's go!
Hey. be careful!
Uh. got a CAPE of 4.000.
- 100 knots gate-to-gate wind shear aloft.
- Come on.
Give us a nice respectable EF1.
I mean. EF2. we'll take it.
Well. an EF2 would be too big.
You have no faith. Praveen.
Just no more of those baby EF0s.
Javi. how's Dorothy's GPS?
Dorothy's coming
in loud and clear.
Are we in the tornado?
No.
No. it's behind us.
- Okay.
- Wait. should I drive faster?
No. no. no. We've got to
drop the barrels in its path.
Are... are we
gonna see the path?
Whoa!
No! Guys!
This is the path.
How close is it?
That's a lot of lightning.
Okay. you guys stay here.
I'll get it. Wait. wait.
Hey. we got to help her. guys.
It's spilling!
We got to hurry!
No. we need leverage to tip it!
Jeb. hurry!
Hey. Kate. you got
muscles and brain...
Brains.
Okay. let's open them up.
Come on.
Yeah!
We're clear!
All right. we got it!
Let's go. let's go!
We got to go!
Okay. we dropped
the trailer. Javi.
- All right. let's see if it takes the bait.
- Come on. come on. come on.
What if there's no tornado?
What if it's just a
dense wave of hail?
Whoo. baby!
We just shot up 10.000 feet!
- Yes!
Okay. that's not a hail wave.
We did it. Kate.
Wait. wait.
It's getting closer.
Sensors rising. 30.000 feet.
The... the polyacrylate
should be active now.
Are the winds weakening. Javi?
Dorothy can't tell you
that. Lagrangian mechanics.
A moving sensor can't give
you the exact measurement
of wind speed. but...
Ah. yeah! 40.000 feet.
Your tornado isn't
shrinking. Kate.
50.000 feet.
Holy shit.
Nah. nah. nah. nah. nah.
This can't be right.
Javi. talk to us.
Talk to us.
Sensors just shot
up 70.000 feet.
- What?
- Uh. the... the NEXRAD velocity
is 200 miles per hour.
That's impossible.
Unless it's an EF5.
Guys.
Guys. whatever's
in there. it's big.
It's big and it's
moving fast. Drive!
You got to get the
hell out of there!
- Go. go. go!
How did it become an EF5?
It's getting closer!
Oh! Look out!
Everybody okay?
- We can't stay here.
- There!
Overpasses are the
worst in tornadoes.
What do we do?
This car's gonna fly. Come on!
Jeb. Addy. Praveen. Kate!
Guys. you got to
get out of there!
Do you hear me?
Kate!
Come on.
Kate. come on!
Where's Praveen?
Kate! Kate!
Come on!
No. Kate!
Addy! Addy!
Come on!
Put your arms around the rail!
Get in! Get in!
Put your arms around the
rail! You're gonna be okay!
It's gonna be okay!
Keep holding on! I've got you!
I've got you.
Kate! I've got you!
Jeb!
The next stop is 42nd Street.
Come along. everyone.
Our regional office focuses
on New York metro weather.
but we can see weather
around the country here.
Now. see these red outlines?
We're having extremely
unusual activity
in this region
called Tornado Alley.
Is a tornado coming
to New York? Oh. no.
Tornadoes are extremely
rare in New York.
Though. we had an EF1 hit
Brooklyn two years ago.
Whoa.
We have 20 full-time
meteorologists...
All right. looks like
we got some rain coming.
Wind speed's
currently at 28 knots.
moving northeast at 15.
We should call in an advisory.
Hey. Debra? De...
The model projects it's
heading into Maryland.
I'll make the call.
Kate. What do you see?
Um...
Wind speeds have
fallen two knots.
Structure is weakening.
Looks like it's all
falling through.
I think it's gonna lose steam.
Let's hold off on any alerts.
Okay. Keep an eye on it.
Kate. There's a guy
here to see you.
He's in the conference room.
Hi. I'm Kate.
Hey. Kate.
Hey.
It's been a while.
After graduation. I
went back to Miami.
Felt like I needed to regroup.
Shit. you wouldn't believe
it. I joined the military.
- You joined the military?
- Yeah.
I was just feeling kind of lost.
I tried reaching out
to you a few times.
Yeah. I'm not great
with communication.
Yeah. I mean. you
know. I figured.
You know. life and all.
But I hadn't heard
from you. so. you know.
I stopped by your mom's
in Sapulpa to check in.
She said... she said you
don't come home anymore.
I knew you moved. but
I didn't expect you
to move somewhere like New York.
New York's great.
I like it here.
People are nice.
Get your ass out of the street!
Most people.
My job in the military was
operating one of these.
Phased Array Radar... PAR.
You know. scanning for missiles.
Leveled up from Dorothy.
Many levels.
This thing was so
powerful and so fast.
I could watch a moth fly
from. like. a mile away.
But I kept asking myself...
What if we point this
thing at a tornado?
Well. Javi. it's the
size of a building.
You'd never be able to
get it close enough.
Until now.
The military. they came
up with portable units.
and they're small.
I got my hands on
a few prototypes.
Yo. my man. can... can I
borrow this real quick?
Thanks. Appreciate it.
Um...
All right. look.
Let's say this... this
is a tornado. right?
My team drives up.
We place a portable PAR here.
It's giving me incredible
high-resolution images.
but th... but they're
still kind of flat.
So what do we do?
My team sets up two
more. here and here.
Now we have a...
A three-dimensional scan.
The most perfect scan
of a tornado ever.
Kate. we can use this data
to save lives back home.
- I mean. this is incredible.
- I know.
And you're the only
person that can get me
close enough to a
tornado to do this.
Javi. I...
- No. I... I don't chase anymore.
- Come on. Kate.
What have you been doing here?
Uh. sitting behind
a computer screen?
Like...
The girl I know. she'd
be going into the storms
while everyone else
was running away.
Well. I'm not that
person anymore.
You have a gift.
Look. I... I can't
do this without you.
Look. I... I... should
really be getting back.
But. um...
it was good seeing you.
You be careful out there?
Kate.
You ever wonder...
why it was us that
made it out of there?
It's gonna be okay.
I got you.
Hey. Kate.
Another town got hit last
night with no warning.
We're having a
once-in-a-generation
tornado outbreak in Oklahoma.
It's coming after
the people we love.
It's getting worse every year.
but now we have a
way to fight back.
Just give me one
week out here. Kate.
I got a good team. but the only
thing that's missing is you.
Call me back.
♪ I left my boots
Out by the door ♪
♪ Like I always do ♪
♪ Same stack of magazines
By the kitchen sink ♪
♪ It's nothing new I
packed my bags... ♪
I'm not gonna lie. I
didn't think you'd come.
Nice upgrade from
the old van. right?
Yeah. how are you
paying for all this?
Got investors. you know.
Storms are getting more erratic.
lot of new housing
developments going up.
so the developers. they
want full-time weather data.
So. anytime a new
building goes up.
I want a StormPAR
radar right there
letting the people know exactly
what the storm's gonna do.
I'm telling you.
I really feel like
we're gonna change
the game. Kate.
What?
No. it's just. um...
business entrepreneur was
not how I saw your future.
And we used to feel lucky if
we could get you to wear pants.
Well. that hasn't
completely changed.
♪ I left you But
you never left me ♪
You got it?
Bring it in. team.
All right.
You guys have all heard
me talk about Kate.
How no one has better instincts.
She's the smartest
person I know.
She's the best.
And you will never work
with a more talented
team than this one.
Look. we got PhDs from
NASA. FEMA. NOAA. NWS.
Oh. you've got the
whole alphabet.
Only the best.
Except for Scott.
my partner here.
He went to MIT instead
of Muskogee State.
But. uh. he makes up for it
with his beautiful.
amazing personality.
Well. Kate's only
giving us a week.
but while we have her. ooh!
It's gonna be the wildest tornado
week you've ever seen. fellas.
Yeah. and everybody with a
$10 weather app knows it.
We got to stay ahead
of this circus.
♪ I keep chasin'
That same old devil ♪
♪ Down the same old
Dead-end highway ♪
♪ Ain't no love in Oklahoma ♪
♪ Just the whistle Of
a lone black train ♪
♪ You'll know when
It's coming for ya... ♪
Hey. StormPAR.
We're live on YouTube.
Say something.
- Blow me. Boone.
- Don't engage. don't engage.
Hey. smile. man.
Science is fun. right?
What's up. Boone?
Who are they?
Chasers out of Arkansas.
Hillbillies with
a YouTube channel.
♪ Ain't no love in Oklahoma ♪
Hey. T! Tell the folks
how you're feeling.
I'm feeling pretty good. Boone.
And if you feel it...
Chase it!
I said. if you feel it...
- Chase it!
♪ Ain't no love in Oklahoma ♪
Oh. it's a beautiful day.
Beautiful day!
Go on! Go on. baby!
- Huh.
Hmm. Okay.
♪ Riding in On the
wind and rain... ♪
That's Tyler Owens.
He calls himself a
Tornado Wrangler.
What does that even mean?
Hey. you tornado nerds!
Who wants a T-shirt?
This means our world
is going to shit.
Okay. we got mugs!
Whatever you put in here. it's
gonna make it taste better.
You're gonna get
thirsty out there.
You look thirsty.
You look sweaty.
Give me some cash.
All right. give me
that. give me that.
Who else wants a mug?
All right. let's get
ahead of this bunch.
Yeah. let me see
this. All right. Kate.
Which storm should we chase?
There's a nice-looking
cell over to the east.
It's. uh. it's been a while.
I... I'll just watch
on this first one.
No. no. Kate. Kate. it's
all right. You got this.
It's why you're here.
All right. all right.
guys. let's go.
Everybody get their
last bathroom break in.
All right. be quick.
fellas. We're on the clock.
Five minutes. then
we're loading up.
Here we go.
Okay. uniforms.
Wrinkle-free shirts.
Crisp hats. Good.
Ah. looks like they're
going to church. man.
- I like it. Right?
- Looking good. looking good.
Hey. man. you're not
gonna hold the door?
Come on. man. Too
heavy? StormPAR.
StormPAR.
All right. see you out there.
Thanks so much.
Come on. Kate. You got this.
What is she doing?
She's doing her thing. man.
You know. I used
to do that. too.
Compare the wind direction
to cloud movement.
Get you a feel for the shear.
Yep. Sometimes the old ways
are better than the new.
What is Owens up to?
You tell me.
So. where you coming in from?
New York.
Well. you're a long way
from home. city girl.
So you like working
for StormPAR?
Tyler. do we know which
storm we're going after yet?
Well. why don't we ask...
Kate.
Hi. Kate. I'm Tyler.
And I'm Ben.
I'm a reporter. doing a piece
on American storm chasing.
- Yeah.
- Tyler's letting me ride along.
Yeah. Ben just had
to promise to write
nothing but good stuff about me.
Good luck with that.
Hang on.
You didn't say which
way we were going yet.
Now. from what I gather.
west. we double our chances.
East. well. it's high
risk. high reward.
Well. go for the reward.
You don't want Ben to
think you're boring.
No. boring is not usually
a problem for me. Kate.
The two cells to the west are
fighting over the same inflow.
They'll choke each other out.
This one to the east has
the sky all to herself.
Moisture. wind shear.
instability.
All the things you need
to give Ben a good show.
City girl knows her stuff. Ben.
I said. city girl
knows her stuff. Ben.
Thanks. Maybe if
I work real hard.
I could be a Tornado
Wrangler. too.
Talk to us.
We want the cells to the west.
Uh. the one to the east
has much better numbers.
Mm. conditions don't feel right.
Cap is too strong.
It'll never break.
You heard her.
Let's move.
All right. let's move. fellas.
All right.
Guess we're listening
to dandelions now.
I thought she told us east.
She going the wrong way?
Nope.
What did the tornado
cowboy have to say?
Exactly what you'd expect.
Oh. updraft is cycling.
Okay. let's take
a right up here.
It's forming just
like you called it.
Scarecrow. Tin Man.
get into position.
Wizard. stick with me.
What's the plan?
So. we want a 3D scan
of the entire area
around the vortex.
which means we're gonna
surround it with three radars.
each one pointed at the tornado.
Tin Man will get
behind the tornado
and plant his radar
on the right-hand side.
Scarecrow is gonna
get behind the tornado
and plant his on the left.
And all the data that they send
will be received by Wizard.
And how about Lion?
We got to complete the triangle.
We get right in front of that
thing and set up our radar.
You got this. Kate.
Just tell us where the
front of the tornado is.
Okay.
That's our tornado. baby!
♪ Took a Nine-Eleven 'Bout
a hundred and seven ♪
All right. what's up. chat?
Welcome back.
Thank you for joining us.
It is a perfect weather day.
We just had tornado genesis.
I'm looking at a tall
rope due north of us.
and she is pretty.
Dumbasses!
It's like the wild.
wild West out here.
♪ Havin' so much fun
That it's probably... ♪
Whoa. whoa. whoa. Okay.
♪ All the boys and
the girls Down there ♪
♪ Sure do know How
to have a ball... ♪
Joining us today. per usual.
- got my chief storm hound. Boone.
- Boonie. baby.
We got Dexter and Dani
in the caravan behind us.
- And Lily with her drone ready.
- What's good? What's poppin'?
What's good?
And our special guest today.
we got Ben in the back seat.
Ben. you just came in from.
uh. London yesterday. right?
Uh. uh. yes.
South London.
J... Uh. just between Streatham
Hill and West Norwood.
Okay.
- Tyler. tornado's on the move.
- Okay.
Oh. yeah!
Oh. it's on now. Ben!
You ain't in London anymore!
Strattonham. Berkshire.
what the hell?
Get me in front of it.
Okay. wait. Uh. we
need to take a right.
Here.
♪ When we lit out of
Fayetteville. they were... ♪
Lion. this is Scarecrow.
Tornado is moving steady at
one-seven miles per hour.
Damn. Dandelion girl was right.
All right. who asked
you. man? Just drive.
Slow down. Keep us
out of the hail.
We got golf balls. baby!
Are those golf
balls or baseballs?
Grapefruit!
I'm assuming this is safe.
♪ All the boys and
the girls Down there ♪
♪ Sure do know How
to have a ball... ♪
Heads up! Okay. okay.
♪ Havin' so much fun
That it's probably ♪
♪ A little bit
Against the law... ♪
You little beauty.
Hey. what are you doing?
That's the Tyler Owens effect.
Wizard. hang back. Get
those hard drives fired up.
Copy that. Wizard hanging back.
The path is shifting.
Okay. there's a right coming up.
This is Tin Man! Approaching
our PAR position!
Ready? One. two. three!
- Lock!
Tin Man is active!
Okay. Tin Man. PAR
data is coming in.
Where. Kate?
We got to be within 300
meters for the radar to work.
Scarecrow's taking position.
Go!
Lock it!
Javi. Scarecrow is active.
Scarecrow is up.
Okay. Scarecrow. we got you.
Waiting on you. Lion.
Okay. take these.
Come on. Kate. talk to me.
talk to me. We getting close?
Just up there in the clearing.
Kate! I need you!
Kate!
Javi. get in!
Get in!
- What is it? What is it? What do you see?
- This isn't right.
Hang on. guys. We're
gonna find a closer spot.
Is this where it's headed?
Javi. I...
We're too far!
StormPAR!
Javi!
What are you doing
out here. man?
Tornado's that way.
Hey. Kate.
Nice goggles. Javi!
All right! Here we go!
Whoa. buddy!
Oh. yeah!
All right. boys. harnesses on.
Harness time!
Oh. yeah. it's my
favorite part. Ben.
- Harness?
- Yeah. we're entering the suck zone. baby.
- Ben. put your harness on.
- I'm doing it.
We're going to a
tornado for God's sakes.
Oh. yeah!
All right. here it comes!
Uh. my harness won't do up.
- My harness won't do up!
- Ben. you got to hurry.
- Damn. Ben.
- Why didn't you tell me this before?
Just put your strap on.
You're a wild man!
- Oh. God!
♪ Across these endless skies ♪
Are those fireworks?
Yep.
Oh. yeah!
Yeah!
How you feeling. brother?
Oh. top of the world. man.
All thanks to my crew.
I got Boone on camera.
We got Lily. Dexter. Dani.
You viewers asked me. "Can you
shoot fireworks up a tornado?"
And the answer is yes.
Yes. you can.
How we doing back there. Ben?
Ben? Oh.
All right. all right.
If you feel it. chase it.
Remember. you kids. do
not try this at home.
We are professional
- Tornado Wranglers.
- Yes. indeed.
He's insane.
Yeah!
- Yeah.
I'm sorry. Javi. I...
I screwed up.
Hey.
We'll find another one.
It's all part of the gig. right?
Yeah. of course.
I'm gonna go check
in with Scott.
♪ Let me ride On
the wall of death ♪
♪ One more time ♪
♪ Let me ride On
the wall of death ♪
♪ One more time... ♪
Haven't we stayed here before?
Yeah. Javi.
we've stayed in every
motel in Oklahoma.
Remember we used to
have Addy check in?
Then later. we'd all
sneak into the room
so we could all save ten bucks?
We'd have Addy do
it 'cause she was...
'Cause she looked so sweet.
Hey. um. you want
to hang out later?
I'll go. you know.
just go into the room real
quick. and. obviously...
shower. and we can
come back out here.
Um. I'm... I'm real
tired. but. um...
maybe another time?
Yeah.
All right.
- Well. good night.
- Good night.
It's good to have you back.
I'm not back.
I remember. One week.
Yeah. We did it.
Here we go. now we gotta top it.
City girl.
Hey!
"The cells to the west
will choke each other out."
she said.
"The one to the east
will put on a show."
Well. didn't throw
you off the scent.
Hey. that's what
makes Tyler famous.
You mean on YouTube?
Uh. y-yeah.
Yeah. we're... we're
on the YouTube.
We got what?
About a million
subscribers now. huh?
Yes. sir.
Uh. Kate what?
Your surname. just in case
I include you in my piece.
Oh. um. just Kate's fine.
She's a tricky one.
Mm-hmm.
Actually. you made
a good call earlier.
The other cell. it looked
stronger. but cap never broke.
What's a cap?
It's a temperature inversion in the
mid part of the lower atmosphere.
It inhibits a
storm from forming.
Right. Okay.
Good.
Where did you guys all meet?
Did you. uh... did you study
meteorology at the U of A?
No. No.
All right. Kate. me?
You know. I just
flow with the wind.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah. I... I never went to.
like. school or nothing.
Um. Tyler. he... he studied
meteorology. though.
Him? Yeah.
You know. he's a cowboy
scientist. you know.
- He's got this natural instinct.
- Okay. Boone.
- He taught me everything I know. so...
- Boone.
You know. our crew's not
like your crew. Kate.
We don't need PhDs and fancy
gadgets to do what we do.
I guarantee you.
these guys have
seen more tornadoes
than anyone else in
this lot combined.
Is that right? Do you think
there's a chance we'll
see one tomorrow?
Oh. yeah. Oh. yeah.
Outbreak. baby.
You know. if you can keep up.
we'll put you in the episode.
Wow.
Where are you chasing tomorrow?
Oh. no. no. no. no. Not
falling for that again.
Kate's from New York.
Can't trust a thing she says.
Well. can always trust a guy
who puts his face on a T-shirt.
Man. Man. that was good.
Oh. my God. look at his face.
That was spicy. wasn't it?
You got to see this. guys!
Y'all got to see this!
Let's go!
This is a 4WARN weather alert.
All right. Oklahoma.
we could be looking at a
record number of tornadoes.
We've been talking
about this for days now.
We'll need to stay weather-aware
with possible major
storms across Oklahoma
over the next 36 hours.
These are the properties that
were wiped out yesterday.
And all the information
we can pull on them.
Hmm.
How about the owners?
Most of the properties
are underinsured
or have no insurance at all.
Uh. we did talk to a few people
who are very interested
in an all-cash offer.
Mm-hmm.
When do you want to head out?
Kate. this is... this
is Marshall Riggs.
We've been working together.
He's one of the StormPAR
investors I told you about.
How scary was that
tornado yesterday?
Not at all.
Listen. can you give
us a couple minutes?
Maybe grab something
to eat or...
And then we can head out.
Well. boys. when's the next one?
Well. nothing's coming
out of that one.
That one? No. no.
No. it's clearly moving
into a stable environment.
Yeah. No low-level CAPE.
Not enough shear to
keep it interesting.
- Yeah. it's gonna die out.
- Not enough moisture to grow.
Where'd you say you learned
how to track storms again?
I didn't.
You know. we're gonna
be stuck here all day
waiting for nothing to happen.
How about we try to get along?
Yeah. you're right.
Tell you what. I'll... I'll
get us a couple of drinks.
What would you like?
Really?
Really.
Wouldn't mind an iced tea.
- Thank you.
- Coming up.
♪ Woo-ha ♪
♪ Grab your gloss
Grab his keys... ♪
Gonna have a lot more materials
to send you before too long.
Let's keep helping
each other out.
We'll be in touch. all right?
- We got to go.
Oh.
All right. Um. look...
- We're almost done here.
- Now. We got something big.
The moisture's hung up here.
so that's where
we want to focus.
Pack up the burritos.
We got a winner.
Lily. get your drone in the air.
We need your video
stream. Ride with us.
- Northwest. ten o'clock?
- That's the one. Let's ride.
Yeah. yeah. yeah.
yeah. yeah. yeah!
Showtime. baby.
Clear!
All right. come on. Cairo!
Let's go. guys! Let's go!
♪ Don't make me do it to ya ♪
♪ Don't make me
Prove it to ya ♪
♪ This ain't my first rodeo
And I ain't losin' to ya... ♪
Damn. Tyler's on it.
♪ This ain't my first rodeo ♪
♪ Come on. please ♪
♪ Too easy. boys are too easy ♪
Ah. Kate must have
seen the storm. too.
They just passed
Dexter and Dani.
So what's the deal with her?
Why don't we focus
on our story. Ben?
Sorry. She's
just... intriguing.
What do you see?
Okay. already has
a nice structure.
Moisture levels are just
right and lots of CAPE.
What else are you seeing?
Flow is clean.
Pulling tons of warm.
moist air from the south.
And when that warm
air and moisture
busts through the cap.
it explodes in the
atmosphere. creating an anvil.
The vertical wind shear
begins to rotate the updraft.
forming a mesocyclone.
Here's the mystery.
We don't know how
a tornado forms.
We see the hook on
the radar. but...
What are all the invisible
factors coming together?
Every little detail that
- has to be perfect.
- Has to be perfect.
And it's a mix of what we know
and everything we
can't understand.
It's part science.
part religion.
Come on. baby. Come on.
- Please. Please. please. please.
- Come on. Come on.
Come on. come on.
come on. come on.
There it is.
Yeah. baby!
There we go. Ben!
- Hey! See that?
- Yeah.
That's a tornado
right there. baby.
Get some photos of that. Ben.
The birth of a tornado.
nature's masterpiece.
Please tell me you guys
are seeing this right now.
Oh!
We got twins! Twins!
We have twins.
Oh. my goodness.
Is... is that normal?
They're rotating.
Wait. there's a name for that.
There's a name. There's a name.
- Shh. Just. hey. just watch it.
- There's a name for that.
Just enjoy it. man.
Fujiwhara Effect!
Oh. they're pulling apart.
One's gonna die out.
Go faster.
You ready?
Let's get our data.
Come on. Javi.
Oh. they got they fancy little
trucks there. don't they?
- Come on. faster! Faster!
- You guys ready to rock?
Let's go!
Whoa!
Come on!
Go for it. Get around him.
Get on his left.
- I'm trying.
- Well. try harder.
- To the right! Come on. come on.
- No. I'm not doing that.
Oh. we got a little bob
and weave going on here.
- Come on. now.
- Nope. nope. nope.
All right. guys. let's
stop playing games.
Let's cut these guys off.
Come on!
I told you. I told you.
Eyes on the road.
There you go. Owens.
All right. which
one's gonna stay?
- Which one's it gonna be. Kate?
- Okay. I'm on it.
All right. Tyler. we
got to make a choice.
Which one are we
going. left or right?
All right. y'all. we
got Tyler Owens here
making a high-pressure choice.
Boone.
Stop filming for a
second? I need to think.
Yeah. no. of course.
Hey. Tyler doesn't want
you to see this. all right?
He's... he's thinking.
All right. Lily.
what are you seeing?
Uh. it's looking like the
inflow is cranking on the right.
Let's go for the right.
Uh. there should be
a road coming up.
All right. we're
taking the right.
All right. right. guys. right.
Why the right?
Well. it's got a strong
inflow of warm. moist air.
Tornado won't have to
work as hard. Benny.
- Go left!
- What?
Take a left!
Going left. Go left. go left.
Javi. you sure? The right
one's got better numbers.
That's a bad move. honey buns!
Who the hell is making
decisions up there. him or her?
Your intriguing girl just
screwed the pooch. Ben.
All right. get us set
up. Boone. Yes. sir.
Gonna fire a couple flares straight
up this thing's ass. Will do.
All right. drone's
on the ground.
Hang on. What are
you... Hey. Ben.
Excuse me. Uh... How are you?
What are you doing?
Lily. I need you up here.
Sorry. These are
my new trousers.
Can you get my foot. mate?
Sorry. Ben.
- It's okay.
All right. how we doing
back there. Boone?
Good.
- Hundred yards to intersect.
- Dexter. hang back.
- Slow. slow. slow. slow.
♪ 'Cause that highway to
hell Is the road I'm on... ♪
All right. Boone.
We ready? Yep. Yep.
God. do we have to
drive into it again?
Nah. Ben. It's driving into us.
Ain't no other way.
♪ On a dead-end road... ♪
Hey. Ben. I'm gonna
need you to hand me
some of them rockets
in the bag. please.
Thank you!
♪ I'm a red-linin'. lowlifin' ♪
♪ Anything but law abidin' ♪
♪ Feels too good to quit ♪
Sing it. Ben!
♪ I'm running off the edge
They say I'm just a wreck ♪
Locked and loaded!
Hey. Boone. I'm having trouble
with this trigger here.
What? What's going on?
Give me the Phillips-head.
All right. here. Hey. Ben.
can you get me some water?
Yeah. feels like it's a little sticky.
- Oh. no.
♪ I'm too far gone ♪
♪ If I'm ever
gonna make it... ♪
Oh. man.
Boone. this is all chocolate.
- Sorry. man.
You got to quit eating
chocolate in the damn truck.
Promise. I'm not gonna
bring no chocolate anymore.
Oh. no. Hey. all right.
we're good to go.
Here we go.
Augers deployed. What?
Oh. no. no. no. no. no!
Yeah!
Let's go!
♪ I'm never gonna make it
On them streets of gold ♪
♪ I got to quit livin' ♪
♪ On a dead-end road ♪
Was that it?
Hey.
We should've went with her.
Whoo. baby. let's go!
That was amazing. Kate.
How did you even know that?
Well. did you see the wheat?
Winds moved to the north.
Just what this one needed.
Scarecrow's up! Scarecrow's up!
Tin Man is up! Go. go. go!
We're all set! Kate. come on!
All PARs are active. Javi.
Javi. it's turning. fast!
How we looking?
Wizard. talk to me!
We lost your radar. Javi.
You got eyes on the tornado?
What was that?
I think I killed some chickens.
Come on!
Thank God. it just grazed us.
Javi?
- Javi. you hear me?
- Yeah. I can hear you.
All right. we got two
radars looking good.
Third one was
getting great data.
We just need to find
it. download it all.
Javi. the... the tornado
is headed to a small town.
They already called it in.
There's nothing we can do now.
But someone might need help.
There's a GPS
tracker on the radar.
We need to find
it before it dies.
Javi. we've got to help.
Ladies and gentlemen.
we're imposing a curfew
for the safety of
everyone in the area.
Unless you're a safety official.
please clear the
area till 5:00 a.m.
Yeah. let us know if you
need anything. all right?
You were right back there.
It's good that we came to help.
I wish we could do more.
Javi. can the data
from the PAR radar
show us how the tornado died?
Yeah. Why?
I don't know.
Maybe we could use it
to prevent all this.
There's the Kate I know.
Hey. look. um. here.
Take the truck. all right?
I'll go deal with
locating the radar.
You should rest.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Come on. buddy.
You got that in a medium?
Was a nice play
on the left twin.
Yeah. well. didn't
help these people any.
Oh. this is. uh... this
is my Uncle Marshall.
This is the. uh.
owner of the bar here.
- How you doing?
- You're the owner?
- Yes. sir.
- Well. I'm sorry what happened.
We're gonna make it
right. Here's my card.
Didn't know StormPAR was
in the business of helping.
Well. from what I see. they're
trying to make a difference.
That's one way of putting it.
What?
Do you even know who
you're chasing for?
- What are you talking about?
- How much more do these people got to lose
before y'all are done
making a difference?
Sorry. says the guy
setting up shop.
selling T-shirts and
mugs after a storm's hit.
Tyler. you have a minute
for some questions?
Yeah. I got a dog to
find. Talk to Kate.
She seems to have
all the answers.
Hey. Boone?
Now's not a good time. Ben.
Kate. Here. take some food.
- Oh. don't have any cash.
- Nah. it's free.
That's why we're always
selling those T-shirts.
- Got some free food.
- Thank you.
Free water. Make sure you
stay hydrated. all right?
Appreciate y'all.
- Oh.
Well. save it. In
case you run low.
Okay. Well. at least
take some water.
- Thanks.
- Yeah. See ya.
It just took everything.
Everything's gone.
Officials are estimating
residential property
damage alone
in the millions of dollars.
How much more damage
will these storms cause?
Forecasters say the
storms aren't done yet.
The Blackwell Public Library
is dealing with
devastating damage.
Some of Javi's crew said you
were staying out by the rodeo.
Thought you might be hungry.
You find the dog?
Of course I found the dog.
How you doing after all that?
I mean. it doesn't matter.
It's those people that...
Yeah. well. you've seen
the worst of this place.
Thought it'd be nice for
you to see something good.
Want to take you somewhere.
Think it might help.
Come on.
♪ O'er the land of the free ♪
Hyah! Hyah!
♪ And the home of the brave ♪
Hyah! Come on! Come
on! Hyah! Hyah! Hyah!
Picking him up on the heel side.
Can we get two legs?
Oh. he slipped a leg.
That'll be a plus five.
The best part is. Stillwater.
they are one of yours.
So send them out with
just a little bit...
You ever see anything
like this. city girl?
You keep calling me that.
You know I grew up on a farm?
Yeah. Sapulpa. Couple
hours from here.
This ain't my first rodeo.
Look at that. I learned
something about you.
So tell me this.
What was your first tornado?
Tell me yours.
I was eight.
Driving with my aunt.
Sirens are going.
All of a sudden. this
vortex just lowers
right down in the
center of the road.
I was just mesmerized.
Then I looked at my aunt.
and she's got this look
on her face. and...
I realized in that moment I
was supposed to be scared.
Were you scared?
Yeah.
Yeah. I was.
Oh. the Tornado Wrangler
is scared of tornadoes.
Okay. Sapulpa.
Do you know him?
I used to compete.
Got my head stomped on
by one too many bulls.
Thought college might
be better for my brain.
You're scared of tornadoes
but not of riding bulls?
Well. tornadoes.
bulls. same thing.
Fear's the reason you do it.
You don't face your
fears. you ride 'em.
♪ That girl She's a
sweet home Alabama... ♪
Were you tracking
cells out this way?
Air feels heavy.
This isn't good.
Ladies and gentlemen.
I just received word
a tornado has touched
down near the area!
We need to evacuate
this arena right now!
Once again. ladies
and gentlemen.
we need to evacuate
this arena right now!
Keep moving. Kate. Come on.
Keep moving. keep moving.
Evacuate the rodeo
grounds immediately!
Once again. a tornado
has just touched down...
Come on. Kate. All
right. you got it.
- I got her. You're all right.
- Come here. come here.
- You're all right. You're all right.
- All right. come on.
Get inside! Get inside!
All right. watch out. watch out.
Whoa. stop!
Stop. stop. stop!
All right. Keep
going. keep going.
Wait. wait. wait!
- Hey. hey. hey!
Okay. just get in
the car. okay. honey?
Hey! Get inside! Ma'am.
stay out of the car.
- Come here.
- Come to Mommy.
Hello. Nothing works
in this shithole.
Now the cable's out.
I can't get a soda from
the vending machine.
- The pool's empty as shit.
- Do you have a storm shelter?
Man. the AC's blowing
hot air. No. I'm sorry.
Can we get a refund going here?
All right. maybe
like a basement.
Do you have a basement?
No.
- There's a line here. buddy.
We need to get these people
underground right now.
Okay. there's no tornado.
Nine times out of ten.
it's a false alarm.
- You hear that?
- Now the power's out.
- No tornado.
- We got to find a shelter. fast.
Hey!
Hey. I don't want to have
to give you a bad review.
- I just started working here.
- Man. I don't want to have...
- Everybody. come with me!
- All right. follow her. follow her.
All right. Ma'am. come on.
Come on. Move. move. move.
- Move. move. move. We got to go.
- Hey. Whoa.
Hey. What?
There's a tornado!
Hey! Let's hop in the Jeep!
Keep going! It's too close!
Let's go! Come on! Let's
go! Go. go. go. go!
Let's go! Come on. get in!
Go! Ah! Get in the car!
Go. go. go. go. go!
All right. go. go!
Come on. honey.
Watch your step!
All right. we got
to move faster!
Keep going! All
right. you got her?
No! No! Stop!
No!
We got to go! We got to go!
Go!
Okay. Okay. hold
on. Come on. honey.
Okay. you got to stay low.
- Cover her eyes.
- Okay.
- Hold on tight! Hold on tight!
- Okay. you're gonna be okay.
- Hold on. honey.
Tyler!
No. Kate! Stay with them!
Help me!
All right. Look at me.
All right. stay down.
Just grab my hand. Come on.
I got you. I got you.
Don't let it get me! Please!
Keep your head down. Just
stay low. Eyes on me.
- I can do it.
- Stay low! No. no. no. no. no!
- No. I can do it.
- No. no! No. no. no!
- Hang on!
- Help me!
Stay down!
- No. no. no. no!
Tyler!
We're gonna be okay!
We're going to be okay!
I've got you.
It's going to be
okay. I've got you.
It's going to be okay.
It's all right.
It's gonna be okay.
I've got you. I've got you.
Tyler?
Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Is it over?
Kate!
Kate.
When I saw the size
of it on the radar
and... and where it was headed.
- all I could think was...
- I'm... I'm all right.
I'm all right.
So where did you stick it out?
Right down here.
Good call.
It's all Kate.
You've been with
Owens the whole time?
Yeah. Why?
Javi.
Apparently. this. uh.
place was family-owned.
so I'm gonna start
working up some numbers.
Riggs is gonna want
those first thing.
Okay. man. I'll... I'll
catch up with you guys.
Yeah.
Javi...
what is Riggs getting out
of all your data collection?
What's... what's it matter?
Is profiting off
of people's tragedy
part of your business plan?
Why are you doing this?
Wait. hold on.
Riggs is offering these people
a way to move on
with their lives.
He's swooping in and
taking advantage of people
who have just lost everything.
You... you have no
idea what that's like.
I don't know what that's like?
How about losing three
of my best friends
while you were trying to land a big.
fat grant for your science project?
Huh.
Kate. Kate. I didn't...
Kate!
Mm-hmm.
Kate. Wait. wait.
Don't leave like this. Look.
Kate!
Where you going?
♪ I been dreamin' ♪
♪ I been drivin' ♪
♪ Trying to stay
Between the lines of ♪
♪ Who I am ♪
♪ And who I used to be ♪
♪ I been livin' ♪
♪ I been losin' ♪
♪ Walkin' miles In
different shoes. and ♪
♪ Findin' out ♪
♪ I can't run from me ♪
♪ And if I ever get
A little too far ♪
♪ I remember Where
I left my heart ♪
♪ Can't take the home ♪
♪ Out of Oklahoma ♪
♪ It's where my soul ♪
♪ Was born to be ♪
♪ No matter where I'm goin' ♪
♪ I'm a wild wind blowin' ♪
♪ Just a-rollin'
Like a tumbleweed ♪
♪ Can't take the home ♪
♪ Out of Oklahoma ♪
♪ So you can't
take it Out of me ♪
Mama. it's me.
Kate?
What happened?
What...
I am sorry there's
so much junk in here.
I'll clear it out
for you tomorrow.
And your friend Javi
stopped by a few weeks back.
Almost didn't recognize
him with the haircut.
You chasing again?
No.
Do you need anything?
No. I'm fine.
Okay.
- Good night.
Here we are.
Oh. hello! Hello.
Hello!
Ahoy! Ahoy!
Kate is doing some
work. as always.
Where is she? Show yourself.
- Isn't she cute?
- What are you doing?
I'm just doing a little
video tour of the barn.
where we do most of our work.
This is Kate's famous
middle school project.
Whoo-hoo.
What is it you're
working on. Kate?
- Tell the folks.
- Uh. cloud microphysics.
Say again? Cloud mic...
Cloud microphysics.
- Guys.
This is what I have
to put up with...
when you're dating
someone who's very bright.
Gorgeous?
- Hey. Jeb?
- Yeah?
- What are we gonna do tomorrow?
- Today?
Uh-uh. tomorrow.
What are we doing?
We're going chasing... Uh. we're
gonna kill a tornado. right?
We're gonna be...
We're taming a tornado.
- We're taming a tornado?
- We're taming it.
This is Kate's favorite slogan.
"Taming a tornado."
This is... this
is what it's like
to be inside a tornado. Kate.
Well. I can only do it with you.
How you doing?
Just the way I left it.
I've been wondering what you want
me to do with all this stuff.
You can just throw it out.
You done? Hmm?
It's funny. I keep seeing
more and more tornadoes
and floods and droughts and...
price of wheat and seed
going up and up and up.
But I'm still here.
I'm sorry. Mom.
I haven't been
good about calling.
I've got to get this. Um...
"Throw it away."
I'm still waiting for
you to save the world.
Build your own
tornado. Look at that.
Middle school
science fair project.
Well. you must've won.
How'd you find me?
Uh. Dexter pieced it together.
He remembered your name from
the news a few years back.
I'm sorry about your friends.
I'm fixing some food. You
two okay eating outside?
Oh. I'm not gonna
bother you. Ms. Carter.
- He's not staying.
- He's staying.
You can call me Cathy.
Kate. why don't you
set up the table?
That only gets you so far.
and every chaser
has to make a guess.
and the good ones have
an instinct for it.
Oh. she had that early on.
Always knew when
weather was coming.
even better than the cows.
Wow. you hear that? You're
better than the cows.
That's a compliment.
Got to have a feel for it.
She always had a feel for it. huh?
- Oh. yeah.
One time. I was
giving her a bath...
- Can we not?
- Maybe just a little.
And we heard thunder. and
she shot up out of the tub
and ran out the house
naked as the day she
was born... Oh. my God.
And I had no idea where she w...
I was terrified.
And when I finally
caught up with her.
she was standing in the
middle of the wheat field.
staring at the sky.
- I got to try that out.
- Will you stop encouraging her?
Keep your clothes on.
Kate. Let your mom finish.
All I'm saying is. she
always loved weather.
Worse the weather.
the happier the girl.
What about you?
Tyler. how'd you
come to do this work?
Well. when you love something.
you'll spend your whole life
trying to understand it.
Katie was studying for a PhD.
Wow.
I keep telling her to
come back and finish it.
Okay. Mom.
She was heading up a big
study with her friends:
disrupting tornado dynamics.
Uh. does anybody need anything?
Nah. I'm... I'm
good. thank you.
'Kay.
Once-in-a-generation
tornado outbreak continues
across Oklahoma.
After that EF4 that
hit Stillwater.
the state will continue to see
more devastating effects...
The Sooner State is bracing
for increasingly
violent tornado...
I invited Tyler to stay the
night in the guest room.
Mom.
You thought you could
disrupt a tornado.
- Hey. don't look at that.
- Oh. you're the OG Wrangler.
Tyler. can you give that to me?
"Using superabsorbent polymers
to reduce moisture
in the updraft.
- trying to collapse it like a house of cards."
- Tyler.
I mean. you'd have to
drop a silo of it in a
funnel for any real effect.
Well. yeah. that's why
we were trying to use
different reagents
to enhance it.
- It's a dumb idea.
- Yeah. some of your reactants are off.
A few of these
solubility rules skew...
What?
You really think I'm
an idiot. don't you?
No. I don't think you're an...
- Hey. modeling's got so much better.
- Tyler.
I can upload this to my laptop.
link up with a supercomputer.
- No. no...
- I'm telling you.
- we can get a new model running.
- That's okay.
- Please. can you stop?
- It's a great idea.
How did you not tell
me about this before?
Because I got it wrong!
In the field. in the moment.
when it mattered.
I got it wrong.
Okay. I underestimated
what we were up against.
and I pushed it too far.
And for what?
Some childish dream I had that
I could make a difference?
It was never gonna work.
And I h... I have to
live with that forever.
You know. uh. EF1 or
EF5 tornado rating...
it's not based on
size or wind speed.
The power we ascribe to it.
it's based on damage.
Now. it's only after the
fact we can really define it.
What it destroys.
what it takes from us.
I'm sorry for what happened.
But how much more
are you gonna let this
thing take from you?
You know. you should...
you should get some sleep.
Don't want to miss
any storms tomorrow.
You said you could get
a new model running?
Yes. ma'am.
So this is an EF1.
perfect conditions.
Run your experiment.
see if it works.
Okay. so. um. 1.500
kilos of polymer
absorbing 300 times its weight.
So. it's. uh. 450.000 kilos
of precipitation loaded into
our water-filled polymer
to load the updraft.
Let's see how the
model responds.
Buoyancy of the rising
air is reducing.
It's reducing.
- Slowing the updraft.
- Temp is going down.
Kate?
Kate. in theory. this
should've worked.
In theory.
But it wasn't an EF1 that day.
I mean... we never
had a chance.
You want one?
Yeah. that's my radio.
What's all this for?
Wait. what are you
touching back there? Stop.
You have a lot of stuff in here.
Yeah. that... that's a mirror.
Oh. God.
- Ooh.
- Have you ever been in a car before?
- You got a lot of gadgets.
- Yeah. yeah. don't touch.
There's... there's guards
there for a reason.
- What do these do?
- That's a...
Oh! God.
- Sorry.
- That's a rocket.
Yep.
All right. what about
these two little ones?
Just west of Enid.
Yeah. but this one to the east
has the sky all to herself.
Yeah. I'm not falling
for that again.
You serious?
Tell you later.
♪ Hotter than A
no-AC-all-summer ♪
♪ Girl. you stole my heart ♪
♪ Steal my thunder... ♪
Dew point is steady!
Wind shear is good!
Holy shit!
Oh. my God. the whole
updraft is rotating!
Holy cow! I mean. look
at those striations!
It's low precip! You
can see everything!
- Aw. she's perfect!
- She's gorgeous.
She's gonna give us
something! Come on!
♪ Like the Mississippi Rose ♪
♪ Gold sunset Is
my silver linin' ♪
♪ Bouncin' off your eyes
Like a couple diamonds... ♪
All right. let's harness up.
Uh. we're just gonna drop the
trailer in its path. right?
I'll tell you later.
Shit.
♪ Girl. you stole my heart ♪
♪ Steal my thunder... ♪
Well. you don't have
to drive into it.
It's really dangerous.
Oh. that's why we
have to drive into it.
- Can't miss from in there.
- Oh. shit.
♪ Rain. rain. come today ♪
♪ Tell the sunshine
To take a break ♪
♪ Gray skies blowin'
in From the north ♪
♪ Whatcha say we go ahead
And lock the doors? ♪
- Now. look. this thing's rated for EF1s. okay?
- Oh. shit.
We got extra weight
on the chassis.
We got anchoring down
two feet. Don't worry.
- I'm a professional.
- You're an asshole.
- Hold on. Hold on!
- Oh. Tyler. this is dumb.
This is really dumb.
Uh-huh. all right.
We got this. Kate.
- Here comes the kick!
- Oh. God!
♪ Two seconds that
heart's Zero to 60... ♪
Oh. God. oh. God. oh. God!
Oh. All right. slowing down.
Anchoring.
Barrels.
Hold on.
Oh! Here she comes.
♪ Girl. you stole my heart ♪
♪ Steal my thunder ♪
Now!
- Did you see that?
- I saw it.
- Holy...
- Uh. did it work?
Oh. right. Uh...
So many belts.
It's not working.
Hungry?
What if it's the model
that's the problem?
How do we create a better one?
Hey. uh...
about what I said earlier.
I didn't mean any of that.
It's fine.
If there's anything I can say
or do to make it better...
Give me your PAR
data. That's a start.
What are you doing?
I'm giving this to her.
What does it look like?
I needed money to
start StormPAR.
That's why I went into
business with Riggs.
I want to help
people. too. Kate.
I really do.
I said what I said 'cause I...
I carry that guilt with me. too.
Every single day
of my life. so...
I'm sorry.
Javi. why don't you
stay and help us?
That way. we could finally
solve this together.
You know. there was a time when
I'd do anything for you. Kate.
Javi. Let's roll.
We got a storm
developing up near Enid.
Team's waiting.
I got to get back to work.
The more data I get.
the better for business.
Sorry I stole your car.
It's all right.
Look...
Be careful out there.
Wow. these scans are impressive.
I mean. it's a complete
map of the chaos.
Tyler. our moisture
numbers are off.
Currently. the polymer is only
absorbing the existing raindrops.
not the moisture
from the humidity.
I mean. we need it to
precipitate out more.
So we need to make it rain.
They were cloud seeding
in Lawton a few years ago
for the farmers.
Yeah. Yeah. silver iodide.
We could shoot rockets of that.
So. the silver iodide converts
the moisture into rain.
and then the sodium
polyacrylate.
we need a lot of it...
would pull the water
from the storm.
increasing the cold pool.
No faster way to
choke a tornado.
Hey. Lily.
Yeah. I couldn't get Boone.
No. we're gonna need
you guys for something.
No. no. no. We'll come to you.
All right.
Is this it?
Or you gonna come back
before you go home?
You know I will.
- Love you.
This is for you.
You have any idea what
you're getting yourself into?
I'm beginning to.
Huh. Thanks.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Oh. Lord.
You finally made it.
Ben. you stuck around.
Turns out. there's more to
this story than I thought.
We got a new ending for you.
Look who it is. City girl.
What's up. Kate?
Finally decided to ditch
all those squares. huh?
Right on.
Mm-hmm. Yep. Y'all
missed a big one. Look.
- Oh. wow.
- See?
Hey. can you. um... Can you
rig that drone to collect data?
I can do that.
Yeah. she can do that.
- Easy. Easy.
Hey. buddy. I'm sorry.
- How do I make it up to you?
- Man. you abandoned me.
I don't know nothing
about no makeup.
How about we launch
some new rockets?
You said rockets?
Hey. Y'all ready?
We need a 40-foot trailer
that's light enough for a pickup
but heavy enough to anchor
barrels in 100-mile-an-hour winds.
Why the hell would
you want that?
Why the hell do we want that?
Well. 'cause when we
drive into a tornado.
we want whatever's
on the trailer
to get sucked into
it. but not us.
You're gonna want aluminum.
Okay.
Dexter. talk to me.
What's going on?
Testing the Goldilocks
principle of a tornado
by modifying the variables.
hopefully disrupting
the process.
Mm-hmm. Okay.
Dani. what does that mean?
- Taming the storm.
- Right.
T. tell us what's going on.
All right. we're
gonna shoot the clouds
with rockets of silver iodide.
Yeah. makes 'em rain. right?
Yep. Rain is what we
need in the updraft.
And then we're gonna take
the sodium polyacrylate
and we're gonna deliver it in
the vortex... Don't touch that.
Increasing the cold pool.
And that does what
to the tornado?
Cuts the fuel. Ben.
Lily.
Oh. look at Cairo looking
all cute and whatnot.
Hey. buddy.
She is your story. Ben.
Get me a copy of that.
Let's get out of here.
Uh. no offense. but I'm gonna
get a ride with someone else.
That's it.
Hell yeah.
- We got it. We got it.
- All right.
Okay. ground speed's at
22. Intercept is northeast.
Look for Siloam Road.
Siloam Road.
Whoa. whoa!
- Come on!
- Hey. what are you doing?
Hey! These storm buttheads
are cutting us off. man.
I told you we didn't need her.
All right. let's
not get distracted.
Let's get these
babies in the air!
I can't see it right
now. I lost it.
It's tracking straight ahead.
I'd say push it.
Get ahead of it.
get ahead of it.
Doppler went dark.
That's probably
a dead cell zone.
Lily. are you above us?
It's getting completely
rain-wrapped.
I can't see a thing.
We just got to push
through this rain curtain.
Oh.
Yeah. I just lost my drone.
Hey. we lost visual.
I can't see anything.
That's all right.
Just keep straight.
I can see the road.
You see the road?
This feels different.
I'm telling you. I
think we should stop.
Just keep going.
We'll get ahead of it.
- Scott. we have to stop!
- Keep going!
- We'll get ahead of it!
- Oh. shit!
Oh. God! It's right there!
It's right there! Right there!
Get down! Get down!
Javi!
Oh. God.
- Oh!
- Hold on. y'all.
Tyler. we got to do something.
Hey! On your left. guys!
It's hitting something big!
Oh. my God.
Oh. my God. Oh. my God.
Wait. wait. wait. We
can't just leave them.
We're not gonna leave them. but
we got to move! We got to move!
Back up. back up. back up!
Dex! Go! Go!
It's flying at us. man!
Go faster! I'm
going. I'm going!
Oh!
Javi.
Oh. God.
Hang on.
Come on. come on.
Hang on. Scott.
Go. go. go. go. go!
Hold on. hold on. hold on.
Is everybody okay?
Yeah.
We're okay.
- Yeah. we're good. man.
- We're moving.
- Are you seeing this?
Look at the size of that thing.
This is good.
No. that ain't good.
That ain't good.
It's shifting.
All right. that's
it. That's the game.
Get off the field!
Okay. guys. there's nothing
we can do to stop it.
but when you get there. make
sure people get to a safe place.
All right. Dani.
where am I headed?
There's... there's a...
There's a kids' park on Main.
Make sure to get
people to basements.
uh. big buildings. no windows.
Stay away from windows.
No cars. all right?
All right. careful. y'all.
Stay safe out there. Copy.
Wizard. come to
us. We're gonna...
We're gonna find a new position.
put these radars down.
They're running from
it. They're scared.
They're not running.
They're heading
into town to help.
Look. we got to go. too.
No. we got our access
road here. on the left.
- Coming up.
- Nah. man. there's a lot of people there. man.
We got... I think we
should follow 'em.
Whose side are you on. man?
You want to go hang out with
your little girlfriend? Go.
But we got the team
waiting for us.
and we got the storm
of a century out there!
- What are you talking about?
- Slow down. stop the tr...
- The people! There's people!
- I don't care about the people!
Stop the truck. Javi!
We're planting here!
We need to go help!
Javi. stop the damn truck!
Good choice.
Tell Riggs we're done!
Damn it. Javi!
All right. run to your mom.
Hey. everyone! Get
inside. all right?
Guys. let's go. go. go!
There's a shelter
down there! Come on!
Hey. no! Leave your
cars! Get inside!
It's not safe here! Come on!
- Hey! Everyone. go inside!
- Let's go. guys.
Guys!
Tyler!
Tyler! Shelters are all full!
We got to get everyone
to the movie theater!
Move! Everybody inside!
Sir. sir. you got to leave
it. You got to leave it.
Leave it. leave it!
Come on. come on!
Let it go. let it
go! Come on. come on!
Guys. it's here! You
got to get inside!
Come on. come on. come on.
come on. come on. come on!
Come on. We're almost
there. I got you.
Come on! Get in.
get in! Come on!
Come on. come on! You
got to go! It's here!
Get inside. everybody!
Come on!
Tyler!
Okay.
Come on.
Watch out!
- You got to get inside!
- I'm not leaving you!
Kate.
Come on. Kate! Lift!
Okay.
- Let's go. let's go!
- Come on!
See if you can find a basement!
I'll check the other side!
There's no basement
on the other side!
There's nothing
over here either!
This theater isn't built
to withstand what's coming!
There you go.
- You got her?
- I got her.
Where's Kate?
Kate!
No. Kate!
- Tyler! Tyler!
- Kate! Kate!
- Tyler!
- Get him in!
Doors!
Damn!
Stay down. stay down. stay down!
Go. go. go! Go. go. go!
That way. that way!
You have to get down!
- Get down!
- That's it. Don't look back.
Don't look back. Keep going.
We got to get these people...
We got to help get these people
to the back of the theater.
Tyler. come on. Come on!
Hey. We got to go. T.
Come on. Come on.
Okay.
Come on. come on. come on.
Take my hand. You
got to get up.
Get back! Get back! Get back!
You're okay. you're okay.
Slow it down. Hold tight!
Get down. get down!
Push in. push in! It's alive.
It's alive! It's alive!
It's alive! Hold on!
Come on. Come on.
Lily! No!
Tyler! Tyler!
Don't let go. don't let go.
don't let go. I got you!
Thank you.
- Are you all right?
- Mm-hmm.
You okay?
Kate.
Careful.
You okay?
Easy.
Is everyone okay?
- Easy. easy.
Is it okay?
- Did it help?
- You did it. Kate.
You did it.
Kate. it worked.
You okay?
Oh. my God. that was
amazing. Oh. my God.
We thought you were
a goner for sure.
You're brilliant.
Mm-hmm.
I think I love you.
I thought for certain
I was gonna fly.
No. you did fly. Honestly.
Door-to-door service.
just like I promised.
- Brought you back in one piece.
- Yeah. just about.
Look. when you get to New
York. with the review board.
they're gonna say that it was
the fire from the refinery
or the smoke or a
million other things
that caused that tornado to
vanish. and that's fine. too.
But the point is.
is that we know
these things can be disrupted.
and we need a whole
new branch of research
on how to harness these storms.
Are you sure you don't
want to do the pitch?
It sounds like
you want to do it.
Nah. Nah. partner.
Go get us that money.
you know what I'm saying?
I ditched Riggs. all
right? Fresh start.
Maybe it's time to
renovate the old barn.
I like that. I like that.
Whoa. Owens!
StormPAR.
Sapulpa.
Still not telling me
when you're coming back?
I don't know. This could be it.
Can't tell if you're
joking or not.
Well. maybe if you feel
it. you should chase it.
Give me a call. all right?
Let me know how it goes.
Safe flight.
Okay. time's up. You
got to move your car.
Yo. come on. man.
Seriously?
- Let me get a. uh. tow truck up here to departures.
- Okay. okay. okay.
Yeah. yeah. yeah. I'm-I'm
gonna move. I'm gonna move.
♪ Down 75 ♪
♪ Just like I been doing
For my entire life ♪
♪ And if I win. gon' have
to Give my baby some ♪
♪ You know that woman
She ain't dumb... ♪
What's going on? Move your car.
Go.
Now.
♪ Run. horse. run ♪
♪ Yah! ♪
Whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa.
whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa!
No. no. no. no.
no. no. no. Hey.
Attaboy.
♪ Yah! ♪
Due to increasing winds
from a nearby storm.
please expect delays.
♪ A rattlesnake kiss ♪
♪ A buzz you get When
the whiskey burns ♪
♪ And the nicotine hits ♪
♪ The devil you know ♪
♪ A taillight glow ♪
♪ Yeah. a heartbreak kid ♪
♪ When you're moving
too slow Come on ♪
♪ The restless wind ♪
♪ You can't fence in ♪
♪ That barb on the wire ♪
♪ That wild in the horse ♪
♪ When you hear that train ♪
♪ When the sirens ring ♪
♪ Better batten down. baby ♪
♪ It's a hell of a storm ♪
♪ Hey. hey ♪
♪ Oh. oh ♪
♪ I'm a renegade rebel ♪
♪ With my pedal to the floor ♪
♪ Hey. hey ♪
♪ Oh. oh ♪
♪ Them boys don't know ♪
♪ I ain't in Kansas anymore ♪
♪ Nah. nah. nah. nah.
nah Nah. nah. nah. nah ♪
♪ Hell nah ♪
♪ I ain't in Kansas anymore ♪
♪ Nah. nah. nah. nah. nah ♪
♪ A movie scene ♪
♪ A fever dream ♪
♪ When you catch your breath ♪
♪ You can come back down ♪
♪ Your torn-up heart's ♪
♪ Like a trailer park But
you still can't wait ♪
♪ Till I come back around ♪
♪ Hey. hey ♪
♪ Oh. oh ♪
♪ I'm a renegade rebel With
my pedal to the floor ♪
♪ Hey. hey... ♪
We are professional...
- Tornado Wranglers.
- Tornado Wranglers. baby.
♪ I ain't in Kansas anymore ♪
You think I'll get my
own face on a T-shirt?
- That'd be cool.
- If you're lucky.
That'd be really
cool. I'd wear one.
- You would?
- Yeah.
All right. Boone.
you take that back.
♪ Never really was one
For relationships ♪
♪ I let love sail away ♪
♪ Always been the first
one Calling it quits ♪
♪ Cowboys never stay ♪
♪ All this rambling
And wandering ♪
♪ Is all that I know ♪
♪ But you make me
feel Right at home ♪
♪ You gave this lonely
life Some meaning ♪
♪ Got this nonbeliever
Believing ♪
♪ Oh. when My
blindfolded heart ♪
♪ Is in the darkest of dark ♪
♪ And my soul is
Searching to see ♪
♪ You leave a light on for me ♪
♪ You leave the
light on For me ♪
♪ Ah. yeah ♪
♪ Ain't it crazy. baby
In a flip of a switch ♪
♪ You get me out of my head ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ And when the shadows
Are coming in quick ♪
♪ You threw 'em
Right off the edge ♪
♪ Oh. I still get lost. yeah ♪
♪ But I don't get gone ♪
♪ 'Cause you always
Lead me back home ♪
♪ You gave this lonely
life Some meaning ♪
♪ Ooh. yeah. yeah ♪
♪ Got this nonbeliever
Believing ♪
♪ Oh. when My
blindfolded heart ♪
- ♪ Is in the darkest of dark ♪
- ♪ Darkest of dark ♪
♪ And my soul is
Searching to see ♪
♪ You leave the
light on For me ♪
♪ Oh. you leave the light on ♪
♪ You leave the
light on For me ♪
♪ Oh. you leave the light on ♪
♪ You leave the light on ♪
♪ You gave this lonely
life Some meaning ♪
♪ Got this nonbeliever
Believing ♪
♪ Oh. when My
blindfolded heart ♪
♪ Is in the darkest of dark ♪
♪ And my soul is
Searching to see ♪
♪ You leave the
light on For me ♪
♪ You leave the light on ♪
♪ You leave the
light on For me ♪
♪ You leave the light on ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-